Guide to the Cornelius W. de Kiewiet papers, 1949-1951.
de Kiewiet, Cornelius W. papers, 1949-1951
- Applications., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  Hastie, John W.; McCrossen, Vincent A.
- Academic Appointments., 1948-49 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  Boorstin, Daniel J.; Kraft, Julius; Konvitz, Milton R.; van der Horst, Dr.
- United States Army., 1949-50 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- United States Air Force., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- United States Army Air Force., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- United States Army., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Associated Research Councils., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  National Research Council; Commission on Human Resources for the Fields of Advanced Training.
- Association of American Colleges., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  Snavely, Guy E. Association of American Universities.
- Association of American Universities., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  Middlebush, Frederick A.; Conant, James B. International Association of Universities.
- Scholar Exchange Programs., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1949-50 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Ingalls, Lester W.; Case, Everett. National Association of State Universities.
- Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities., 1949-51 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Association of Governing Boards of State Universities and Allied Institutions., 1947-50 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Babcock, Howard E.; Noyes, Nicholas H.
- Association of Land-Grant Colleges and, 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  Universities.
- Associated Universities., 1948-51 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Fackenthal, Frank D.
- Atlantic Union Committee., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  Roberts, Owen J.
- B Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Berkman, Theodore; Bennett, Pearl; Blanding, Sarah Gibson. Brookings Institution.
- Neal Dow Decker., 1949-51 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Booth, Ferris.
- Brookhaven National Laboratory., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- C Miscellaneous., 1949-51 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Schultz, Andrew; Wolfle, Dael; Case, Everett; Crofts, Frederick S.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Collyer, John L. Campus Club; Commission on Human Resources for the Fields of Advanced Training; Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion; New School.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1948-51 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Gardner, John W.; Dollard, Charles.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1948-49 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Fox, Edward W.; Collyer, John L.; Baldwin, William M.; Dollard, Charles; Rossiter, Clinton L.; Brooks, Earl. Communism; American Way of Life Program.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Lester, Robert M.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1948-49 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Failing, Jean; Gardner, John W.; Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Gibson, Anson W.; Alien, Lucile.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  Williams, Robin M.; Lester, Robert M. Study of Student Attitudes.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1948-49 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Carnegie Corporation., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Leighton, Alexander H.
- Christmas., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Civil Defense., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- College Entrance Examination Board., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. Barber, Joseph. South Africa., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- College Entrance Examination Board., 1949-50 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  Adams, Arthur S.; Fels, William C.
- Commission on Financing Higher Education. Fackenthal, Frank D. Association of American Universities., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Communism., 1948-50 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Lamb, Leo; Steinhart, Victor Gibson, Edwin T.; Noyes, Nicholas H. Gould, Abbott; Phillips, Herbert J. Day, Edmund Ezra; Flanigan, Horace C.; Menjou, Adolphe; Daniels, Whitman; Hodgkins, H. F.; Morrison, Philip; Upson, Maxwell M.; Kazakevich, Vladimir D.
- Conferences, 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Corning Conference, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  American Council of Learned Societies.
- D Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  Donlon, Mary H.; Robeson, Paul (Mrs. ); van Deusen, Glyndon G.; Danielian, N. R.
- Arthur H. Dean., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  Gannett, Frank E.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Meigs, Robert B. Arthur Dean and the Cornell Presidency.
- Deans ' Group., 1948-50 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Displaced Persons and Refugee Students and Professors., 1948-49 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  Zook, George F.; Kerr, Donald C. American Council on Education.
- E Miscellaneous., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  Emanuel, Victor; Ellingson, Mark; Eisenhower, Milton S.; Edwards, Harold T. Engineering College Research Council; Rochester Institute of Technology.
- Economic Cooperation Administration., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Economic Cooperation Administration., 1947-50 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  Becker, Neal Dow. Carnegie Corporation; International African Institute.
- Foundation for Economic Education., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  Read, Leonard E.
- Francis P. Eagan., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Victor Emanuel Lecture Fund., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Victor Emanuel., 1949-50 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  Dean, Arthur H.; Gubb, Larry E.; Emerson, Willard I.; Morrison, Philip; Hoover, J. Edgar. Communism; Federal Bureau of Investigation.
- F Miscellaneous. Fulton, Creed W.; Fleischer, Sylvia H. Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs., 1948-51 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- National Research Council Committee on Asian Anthropology., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- United States Dept. of State., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  Brannan, Charles.
- United States Federal Government., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Federal Government - Letters to Congress, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- United States Office of Education., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Federal Aid to Education., 1949-50 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Federal Funds to Colleges and Universities., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Ford Foundation., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  Keppel, Francis; McPeak, William; Wright, Theodore P. Fund for the Advancement of Education.
- Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  Jones, Lewis Webster.
- Federal Government Selective Service System., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- G Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Gannett, Frank E.; Graham, Frank P.; Gubb, Larry E.; Galbraith, John S.; Gannett, Caroline Werner; Goodwillie, Edward E.; Myers, William I.; Greenawalt, William E.
- State University of New York., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- H Miscellaneous., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Huzar, Eleanor G.; Hurd, T. Norman; Halsted, Arthur. Human Relations Area Files, Inc.
- Honorary Degrees., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Human Events., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- James H. Hyde., 1950-51 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- I Miscellaneous., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Institute of Pacific Relations; Iran Foundation.
- Institute of Pacific Relations., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Institute of Current World Affairs., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Institute of International Education., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Shank, Donald J.
- Ithaca, New York., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
- Ithaca College., 1950-51 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Job, Leonard B.
- Community Chest. Treman, Robert E., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Ithaca, New York - Common Council, Tompkins County Health Center., 1946-47 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- J Miscellaneous., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Juniata College.
- Japan Miscellaneous., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Keio University.
- Gousta Jaryc., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- K Miscellaneous., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Keio University; University of Kentucky.
- L Miscellaneous., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities.
- Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory., 1947-50 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Morrison, Philip; Feynman, Richard P.
- M Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Morris, Evan J. McCormick Historical Association.
- Mullen Foundation., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- University of Michigan Law School., 1948-49 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Milbank Memorial Fund., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- N Miscellaneous., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  National Commission on Accediting; National Industrial Conference Board; National Bureau of Economic Research; New York State Historical Association.
- National Education Association., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
- National Emergency - Educational Acceleration., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 29-35)
- National Machine Tool Builders' Association., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- National University Extension Association., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- National Research Council., 1948-51 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- National Science Foundation., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- NROTC., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- United States Navy., 1948-50 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- NROTC., 1946-51 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- New York State Citizens Council., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  Eckel, Rhea M.
- O Miscellaneous., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  O'Brien, Henry L.
- P Miscellaneous., 1949-51 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  Cornell Behavior Farm; American Psychiatric Association.
- John S. Parke., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  Becker, Neal Dow.
- Portraits., 1950-51 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Emanuel, Victor; Babcock, Howard E.; Childress, Robert B.
- Questionnaires., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- R Miscellaneous., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  Fox, Edith M.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Rabson, Barrie. Regional History Collection.
- Robinson Airlines., 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  Wright, Theodore P. East Hill Airport.
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1948-50 (Box 10, Folder 51-52)
  Stevens, David H.
- Rockefeller Foundation Grants., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1948-50 (Box 10, Folder 54-68)
  Stevens, David H.; Marshall, John; Wright, Theodore P.; Weaver, Warren; Biggerstaff, Knight.
- Readex Microprint Corporation., 1948-49 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  American Historical Association Committee on Documentary Reproduction.
- S Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Scheetz, Francis H.; Statler, Alice M.
- Sloan-Kettering Institute., 1950-51 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Social Education - Journal of the National Council for the Social Studies., 1949-50 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Social Science Research Council., 1950-51 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Southern Regional Education., 1949-50 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Speaking Engagements., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Students Dropped., 1949-51 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Taylor, Myron C.; Farrell, Thomas M.; Button, Charles C.
- Salary Scale., n. d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- New York State Regents., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- T Miscellaneous., 1950-51 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Treman, Robert E.; Tead, Ordway; Taylor, Myron C.; Teagle, Walter C.; Wright, Theodore P. Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA).
- Teagle Foundation., [1927]-1949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- U Miscellaneous., 1949-50 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- United Nations., 1949-51 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- UNESCO., 1949-50 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- United States Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- United States Concrete and Soils Laboratory., 1948 (Box 11, Folder , 18)
- V Miscellaneous., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  Verity, Calvin. Vicious Circle.
- W Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  Walker, Morton Blaine (Mrs. ); Waddington, Margaret; Wells, Ken. University College of the West Indies.
- J. Carlton Ward., 1949-50 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Fried, Jerome A.
- Watamull Foundation., 1947-48 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Westinghouse Corporation., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  White, Philip M.; O'Connor, D. J.
- Y Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  Griswold, A. Whitney. Yale University.
- Yale Institute of International studies., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Cornells W. de Kiewiet - Personal., 1950-51 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Cornelis W. de Kiewiet - Speeches and Statements., 1948-50 (Box 11, Folder 27-28)